tlvmedia.com 2016-12-01

# TLVMedia | Privacy

Thank you for visiting www.tlvmedia.com (together with all content on the site including subdomains and other websites operated by TLV Media Online Ltd. or its affiliates (“ **TLV Media** ”), the “ **Site** ”). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site. 
1\. **Introduction**  
We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (' **Personal Information** ') you share with us. 

“Personal Information” means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, personal profile, a home or other physical address, an email address or other contact information.

Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to information available on our Site. However, in order to provide you with certain services, you may use the contact form and signup pages on the Site to provide us with your email address and other specified information. 

2\. **Cookies and TLV Media's Ad Targeting Services  
**As part of our services, TLV Media has developed a platform for advertisers and publishers that uses cookies and other tracking technologies to provide non-personally identifiable preference information regarding user web browsing activity on our Site and on our clients' sites (the 'Service'). A cookie is a small text file that is assigned to you the first time you are served an ad and is stored in a file on your computer. Cookies help categorize likely consumer interest segments for use in online advertising by measuring how users utilize a website and the effectiveness of an ad. For example, this information may include the number of visits to a particular website, average time spent viewing such website, pages viewed, navigation history through the website, and other statistics. This information can then be used to better cater to users' needs. 

Cookies are intended to enhance your experience of a website by helping to deliver to you ads in which you are more likely to be interested and by allowing advertisers to ensure that you are not repeatedly served the same ads. In addition, optimizing and customizing advertising to you and other website visitors allows website owners to generate more advertising revenue. This revenue pays for the free content that they may publish for you, or free services that they may deliver to you.

However, neither TLV Media nor its third party ad serving party needs cookies to deliver ads to you, and most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.   
**Our cookies cannot be used by TLV Media, our clients, or by any other party to access any other data on a user’s hard drive, or to personally identify them.**

3\. **Choice**

You can stop cookies from being stored on your computer, and thereby stop TLV Media from using information collected by our cookies by blocking all cookies (from TLV Media and all others) by globally or selectively disabling cookie use in the browser configuration. 

4\. **Personal Information and Anonymous Information**  
If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site, then we will use your Personal Information to improve our services to you, to contact you and to identify and authenticate your access to the Site’s services that you are authorized to access.

We may use Anonymous Information (as defined below) or disclose it to third party service providers, to improve our services and enhance your experience with the Site and its services. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners, for purposes including, but not limited to, targeting advertisements. 

“ **Anonymous Information** ” means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of our Site and services. 

5\. **How We Use and Share Your Information**   
TLV Media may use and share your information: (i) to enable third party service providers to assist or facilitate in the services we provide to our clients; (ii) to comply with comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (iii) to enforce our Terms of Use, including investigations of potential violations thereof, or to protect our rights; (iv) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues; (v) to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of TLV Media, its users, yourself or the public; (vi) with other entities of TLV Media and third party marketing partners; (vii) with third party research companies, vendors, administrative service providers, technology providers, and selected partners for data validation, aggregation, enhancement, verification and suppression purposes, and for research, marketing, advertising, and data aggregation purposes; (viii) for any other purpose for which you provide consent.

In addition, we may also share information with advertisers, publishers and other third parties for marketing and advertising purposes, but such information does not include Personal Information except if you provided it as described above. These third parties may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. 

6\. **How We Store Your Information**   
We may retain information regarding ad delivery for up to 12 months. However, TLV Media may retain aggregate statistics, reports and summaries regarding ad delivery for a longer period. We may delete any or all information regarding ad delivery that relates to you at any time and in our sole discretion, notwithstanding our normal data retention policies. Further, we reserve the right to retain and use any information described in this Privacy Policy as reasonably necessary to comply with laws or regulations, notwithstanding any limitations described in this Privacy Policy to the contrary. Any updates to this Privacy Policy concerning our retention data policies shall apply to all data retained by TLV Media following such update. 
7\. **Links to Other Sites**   
Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. 
8\. **Children's Privacy**   
The Site is not structured to attract children under the age of 18. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age. 
9\. **In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**   
In the event that TLV Media is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used. 
10\. **Commitment**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and TLV Media's Site and Service are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@tlvmedia.com . **  
While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.** 
11\. **Your Consent  
**By using this Site or Service, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to TLV Media's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site and Service. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time, which change will be effective 10 days following the modification. Your continued use of our Site or Service following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. 
12\. **Your California Privacy Rights**   
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of TLV Media who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to support@tlvmedia.com. 

Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year. 

Last modified: December 18, 2012 

**Optout**

If you are not interested in seeing customized ads based on your internet usage preferences, you can opt out by having TLV Media place an opt-out cookie on your browser, to signify you are not interested in seeing targeted ads served by us. If you make any changes to your cookies preferences, remember to check whether your opt-out is still valid.

You also have the option of changing your privacy settings via the [DAA](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or [NAI](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) opt-out services, which let you opt out of targeted behavioral targeting served by TLV Media and other participating companies.
